TEN (ENVELOPE)
[narrator] Ten:
The ability to envelop your body
in a shroud of Nen aura,
making it tougher and slowing
the effects of aging.
ZETSU (SUPPRESS)
Zetsu:
A technique which shuts off
your flow of Nen-aura.
Effective for concealing your presence
and recovering from fatigue.
REN (REFINE)
Ren: A technique for creating
an especially strong Nen aura.
It is crucial for increasing your power.
HATSU (RELEASE)
Hatsu:
The release of your Nen aura,
after using Ren to boost it.
These four elements
are known as the Four Exercises
and are critical to the mastery of Nen.
FOUR EXERCISES
[theme song playing]
You see my double is no mere illusion.
It’s real.
Just as real as I am
until I make it vanish.
You must know this.
You felt it strike against you.
To put it simply
you are going to have to
face two of me at once!
Now behold the culmination
of my mastery of Nen.
The True Tiger Bite Fist!
A x SURPRISING x WIN
[narrator] Kastro used Nen
to create a double of himself.
And his special attack -
the True Tiger Bite Fist
has severed Hisoka’s right arm.
Which of these contenders
will emerge victorious?
[smirks]
[grunts]
[Cocco] Now what?!
Hisoka has covered his right arm
with a scarf?
Shall I demonstrate
my powers of clairvoyance?
[grumbles]
[Cocco] Wow!
Wow! His right arm disappeared
and now cards are raining down!
What is he doing?!
[Hisoka]
The cards you see go from one to thirteen.
I want you to pick a number
and visualize that card in your head.
He’s doing a ‘pick a number’ trick?
[Hisoka] Ready?
Once you’ve selected your number,
I want you to add four to it,
and then double the resulting sum.
After that subtract six and divide by two.
Lastly, subtract your original number.
Now, what do you get?
Gimme a sec…
Did… he say subtract six?
Ahh! I forgot already!
I knew your answer
even before you arrived at it yourself.
[audience gasping in shock]
The number you chose…
was one.
He’s totally right; it was!
How did he know?
Really?!
[Cocco] What?! He’s insane!
This is the devil’s magic!
And he’s incorporated his own injury
into the trick!
I don’t get it.
Why is he so calm?
There are no points for tricks.
It doesn’t have anything to do
with the match.
But still, he’s performing magic!
That’s the bizarre behavior
we expect from Hisoka!
Would you like a souvenir?
You fool!
I will sever your left arm,
so that you’ll never be able
to mock anyone again!
You must not have heard me.
You can take it.
I’ll be more than happy to oblige!
[Cocco] Whoa! One of the Kastros
is charging forward!
[Kastro roaring]
[Cocco] This is unbelievable!
Hisoka has actually sacrificed
his remaining arm!
What in the world is this guy thinking?!
Wait, what?!
So, you did attack with your double.
How interesting.
If you had come at me yourself,
I was fully prepared to counterattack…
by using this.
[audience murmurs]
[Cocco] What? His severed right arm
is back together again!
But how?
[chuckling]
It’s another magic trick.
Can you guess the secret behind this one?
He’s lying.
It’s obvious he’s using Nen
to accomplish this feat.
But... what kind of ability is this?
[Hisoka chuckles]
[Hisoka] What's wrong?
Are you scared?
You’re surprised
because you don’t know the trick.
But that’s magic.
See your power to create a double
is magnificent.
But now I understand how it’s done.
[grumbles]
[Hisoka] I can anticipate
how you’ll attack with your double.
Not to mention,
I know how I should respond.
It’s too bad, really.
You had the potential
to become a skilled opponent...
and that’s why I decided to let you live.
I predict...
you’re going to dance yourself to death.
[growling]
[shouts] Shut up!
No! How did he pick me out?
Doubles are made
from the image the original has in mind,
which is why they tend to be pristine.
But you can’t reproduce the grime
that builds up during combat.
Oh…
Had you not realized that yet?
[roaring]
[groans]
[Cocco] What is going on here?
I’m seeing it,
but I can’t even begin to understand it!
Is this another one
of Hisoka’s magic tricks?
Don't bother.
I hit you square in the lower jaw,
so you’ll be stunned for a minute or two.
[dazzled groaning]
And that means you’ll be helpless
to avoid my next attack.
What?!
Where did this attack come from?
I don’t have time for this.
I have to produce my double
to block the cards!
You can’t make another double.
Creating a new double using Nen
requires intense focus.
The only reason you were able
to produce and release them freely
was that up until now...
you were in a normal state of mind.
Using Nen to replicate
and manipulate something
that’s as complex as the human body,
is extremely difficult.
How difficult, you ask?
By the time you’ve learned
to use a double,
you’ve forgotten how to use Nen
for anything else.
Sad, really.
It’s a little something
I like to call “memory overload”.
You only lost because...
you squandered your memory capacity.
[cheering]
[Cocco]
Kastro’s down and he’s not getting up!
Hisoka wins by knockout!
Hisoka…
[cheering]
[Machi] Nice job.
Well? Hurry up and show me your injuries.
I was never quite sure before
but today’s match proved it to me.
Hm?
[Machi] You are an idiot.
That’s quite possible.
Why did you decide
to put yourself in danger this way?
What was that?
Performance art or something?
Well…
Okay. You’re paying me,
so I guess I can’t complain.
First, I’ll need to stop the bleeding.
[Hisoka] Hey…
Be gentle, if you don’t mind.
Yeah, whatever.
Turn off your aura.
[smirks]
[Machi] I’ll start with your left arm.
Here we go.
Starting Nen Stitches.
NEN STITCHES
There. All done.
Bones and blood vessels,
nerves, and muscles.
They’re basically all connected, now.
Ahh! That’s brilliant.
[Machi] Next…
I’ll do your right arm.
You can hold it yourself this time.
[Hisoka impressed] Mm.
This is always so fascinating to watch.
I so enjoy getting to see
your Nen stitches in action
that maybe I injured myself on purpose.
Fine, whatever.
Twenty mil for the left one,
fifty for the right one.
All right?
Now. Fork it over.
I’ll transfer it
directly into your account.
All right.
And you can treat
the rest of the injuries yourself.
[Hisoka]
Your bedside manner could be better.
You should be able to manage
with your Bungee Gum...
and your Texture Surprise.
Ah.
I guess I should conceal them.
If I do...
they’ll think my arms
were healed magically during the match.
This is nothing more
than an ordinary scarf.
I use Bungee Gum
to attach it to my arm,
then Texture Surprise
to create a layer of skin.
[Machi] He’s so fast.
Fast enough to fool a Nen master
into believing
the arm had actually healed
before he thought to take a second look.
Next, I’ll do the left.
Bungee Gum.
ELASTIC LOVE
BUNGEE GUM
He modifies his aura,
making it both elastic and sticky.
It stretches extremely well,
contracts swiftly when needed,
adheres to most substances
and it can be removed at any time.
Oh, by the way
I call this trick ‘Bungee Gum’
because that was the name
of my favorite chewing gum
when I was a child.
Yeah, you really didn’t need
to tell me all that.
Texture Surprise.
He combines his aura with imagery
in order to reproduce
the appearance of skin.
FLIMSY LIES
TEXTURE SURPRISE
It’s essentially a high-quality copy,
so you can tell it’s fake
if you actually touch it.
But Hisoka probably finds
that drawback exciting.
I call this one Texture Surprise
which comes from the gag stickers
that were included with a popular snack
not too long ago.
Like I said,
I really didn’t need to know all that.
Weren’t you impressed
by my application of these abilities
during the match?
I was almost certain you were.
[Machi] Huh?!
Well, you did see everything, didn’t you?
Yeah… I think I did…
You started with a misdirection,
tossing 13 cards into the air.
At the same time you threw your arm,
attaching it to the roof with Bungee Gum
and the scarf to the ground the same way.
But you didn’t let go.
The aura from each was connected
to the stump of your right arm.
And that’s not all.
The cards you threw as a distraction
were also secured to the ground
with the ends of the 13 strands of aura
connected to your left hand.
And then,
when you threw the ace of spades
at Kastro…
Would you like a souvenir?
Cocco]
… the aura in your left hand was released.
They connected.
All 13 of the aura strands
you had been holding,
stuck to Kastro’s body.
Correct.
You’re much more observant
than Kastro was.
[Machi] I also noticed
that you employed one
of the basic techniques of Nen Zetsu -
to help make your aura almost invisible.
Yes. However, there was one weakness.
[Machi] Yeah.
Pretty much anybody who’s learned Ren,
another basic Nen technique,
could have detected it easily…
by focusing the aura in their eyes
and watching.
That’s why you used
that crazy magic trick of yours
to throw him off guard
while you just stood there,
smiling and pretending to be nonchalant.
It even worked as a kind of camouflage.
You had him convinced
that your lack of aura
was a sign of confidence.
Once you were satisfied
that everything
was going according to plan,
you surreptitiously extended a thread
of aura from your left hand,
the one holding the cards
and connected it directly
to Kastro’s chin.
Everything was ready.
You’d already used Texture Surprise
to alter the scarf on the floor
to resemble human skin.
And so,
when Kastro attacked your left arm,
you activated the Bungee Gum
between your right arm
and the scarf on the floor.
Your arm was restored
and the scarf concealed the wound,
leaving everyone convinced
your right arm
was magically back.
However, this performance
had the unfortunate effect
of bringing Kastro back to his senses.
It made no sense for a severed arm
to simply reappear,
especially in pristine condition.
It was then that Kastro realized
I was actually using Nen
to accomplish these feats
and not magic,
as he was led to believe.
That’s true.
But you didn’t miss
the ever-so-subtle change
in his psychological condition.
See your power to create a double
is magnificent.
But now I understand how it’s done.
[grumbles]
[Hisoka] I can anticipate
how you’ll attack with your double.
Not to mention,
I know how I should respond.
It’s too bad, really.
You had the potential
to become a skilled opponent...
and that’s why I decided to let you live.
[grumbles]
[Machi]
You saw that Kastro was about to recover.
I predict...
you’re going to dance yourself to death.
[Machi]
But then you pushed him over the edge.
[shouts] Shut up!
No! How did he pick me out?
You can’t reproduce the grime
that builds up during combat.
[Machi] And just like that,
you were able to expose
the weakness of his doubles.
But if he had just stayed
calm and composed,
then he actually
would have had a fighting chance.
However...
Kastro couldn't bear the mental strain.
[roaring]
And so... he lost.
You do realize
just how perfect both of those abilities
are for someone like you, don’t you?
They’re practically tailor-made.
As opposed to Kastro’s double ability,
my techniques are so adaptable
that they don’t lose their effectiveness,
if my opponent knows about them.
[Machi] Well...
I’m heading back now.
Already?
Yeah, why stick around
after the job is done?
There’s only so much
that Nen Stitches can do,
so try not to overdo it
until your arm is firmly attached.
Oh, right...
I came here for a reason.
Hm?
[Machi] The message has been changed.
All Troupe members
are to be in York New City
by noon, August 30th,
not just those
who don’t have anything better to do.
[Hisoka] Will the boss be coming?
[Machi] Probably.
This could turn out
to be our biggest mission yet.
So, know if you blow it off,
the boss might hunt you down himself.
Now that is scary.
Oh, by the way…
-Care to join me for dinner tonight?
-[door closes]
What a pity.
-[gasps]
-[door opens]
Killua! So how was Hisoka’s fight?
Tell me!
Boring. Don’t worry,
you didn’t miss much.
Boring?
And Hisoka? Did he win?
Okay, I was lying.
Huh?
[Killua] It was an incredible fight.
Hate to say it
but I watched Hisoka win
and I still don’t know how.
You seriously couldn’t tell how he did it?
Gon.
You and me…
we’ve got to learn all that we can
about Nen.
Yeah!
[Machi] He’s such a mystery.
He never talks about his past.
It doesn’t interest him.
He’ll probably forget
what Kastro looks like by tomorrow.
He doesn’t belong to anything or anyone.
He’s his own man,
no doubt about it.
Because he’s absolutely convinced
that he’s the most powerful.
[tap squeaks]
[wet feet slapping on the floor]
Hmm...
Oh, I forgot to take... this off.
A spider?
I found some new toys to play with.
Time to start the hunt.
[narrator] Hisoka has been masquerading
as a member of the Phantom Troupe.
But to him,
the Phantom Troupe
is nothing more than another target.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] ...Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today we meet Kastro,
who uses the Tiger Bite Fist.
He makes a double of himself with Nen.
Those aren’t easy to deal with!
With this double,
I can use the True Tiger Bite Fist!
[both] Scary, isn’t it?
Next time:
An x Empty x Threat.
Achoo!
Do I have a cold?
[Killua] I bet someone's talking about you
behind your back.
[Gon] Aunt Mito?